Art Collins Papers ARC.0001
Library and Archives
- Series I: Iggy Pop [RESTRICTED], 1985-2005, undated
  - James, Pam, name change, 2001 September 21 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Iggy Pop Europen tour, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 86-88)
  - I Need More, French book, La Serpent A Plumes, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - "Passenger," New World Disorder, 2001 February 21 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Freddy Got Fingered, Tom Green movie, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You," Jazz on Cinema, Volume 2, 2001 February 26 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - "Lust For Life," Nikki Cox, 2001 February 6 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - "Passenger," As Heard on TV, 2001 March 3 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - "Lust For Life," Kellogg's Canada, 2001 March (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Save the Last Dance, "Bad Boyz", 2001 February 27 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - "Lust For Life," Armed Forces in Spain campaign, 2001 March 2 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Ackerland, Jonas, movie, Spun, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Apple Computer, Maria Conte, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Max, Glenn, U.K. Meltdown (Nick Cave), 1995, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - "Beside You," Mark Romanek DVD, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - "Lust For Life," Royal Caribbean renewal, 2001 January (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - "Lust For Life," Drew Carey Show (Bug Music), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - "Passenger," Best Rock Anthems, 1998 March 12 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - "Real Wild Child," Axion Beach Rock compilation, Belgium, 2001 April 23 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - "Ann" sample, Super Furry Animals, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - "China Girl," Rock and Roll Jeopardy!, 2001 April (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - "Aisha," Playstation, 2001 May 3 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - "Lust For Life," Kellogg's Vive cereal, 2001 May 3 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - "Lust For Life," MTV True Life: I'm a Private Wrestler, 2001 April 18 (Box 10, Folder 110)
  - "Passenger," Guinness Draught, Bug Music, 2001 May 7 (Box 10, Folder 111)
  - "Passenger," Proximus (Belgium), 2001 April 10 (Box 10, Folder 112)
  - "Search and Destory," The List (#336 and #441), 2001 March 30 (Box 10, Folder 113)
  - Miller Draft, "Success," (Bug Music), 2001 March 30 (Box 10, Folder 114)
  - "Lust For Life," Essential Soundtracks, South Africa, 2001 April 4 (Box 10, Folder 115)
  - "Living on the Edge of Night, Was Het Nu 70 of 80 of 90, 2001 April 6 (Box 10, Folder 116)
  - "Passenger," Driving Rock compilation, 2001 March 26 (Box 10, Folder 117)
  - "Lust For Life," Ontario Power, 2001 March (Box 10, Folder 118)
  - "Lust For Life," V2 Records / Japan, 2001 February 13 (Box 10, Folder 119)
  - VH1 All Access: 25 Years of Punk, 2001 March (Box 10, Folder 120)
  - "Lust For Life," As Seen on TV, 2001 March 30 (Box 10, Folder 121)
  - "I'm Sick of You" lyrics, circa 2001 (Box 10, Folder 122)
  - Condé Nast display, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 123)
  - Bomp! Records / Bug Music merchandise royalties, 2001 February 6 (Box 10, Folder 124)
    Related materials providing content on Bomp Records may be found in the following collections in this repository: Bomp! Records Collection.
  - U.S. tour report: final, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 125)
  - Canal + Belgium concert TV rights, 2001 April 18 (Box 10, Folder 126)
  - Sigworth, Sig, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 127)
  - Walmart "Artist Cards" catalog, 2001 April (Box 10, Folder 128)
  - Virgin deadlines, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 129)
  - "Mask," Da Mob, Bug Music / Virgin, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 130)
  - "Passenger," Classicos De Classicos, Argentina, 2001 December 4 (Box 10, Folder 131)
  - "Candy," Classicos De Classicos compilation, Argentina, 2001 December 4 (Box 10, Folder 132)
  - Joey Ramone Project, "Memory Book," Dave Frey, 2001 November 12 (Box 10, Folder 133)
  - Laurel Canyon film, Iggy, Sarandon, Bowie photo, 2001 October 22 (Box 10, Folder 134)
  - Stein, Mandy, Journeyman Pictures movie release, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 135)
  - Rock-It Cargo [RESTRICTED], 2001 November 27 (Box 10, Folder 136)
  - Apple Computers, Fall 2001 advertisement option (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Mircosoft memo, 1996 May 28 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - "Beat 'Em Up," Gotham multi-media game, Microsoft, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "Passenger," Xbox - The Soundtrack, 2001 September 13 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Benson, Eric, American Express [RESTRICTED], 2001 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Benson, Eric, telephone charges [RESTRICTED], 2001 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - "Gimme Danger," Boss Clothing, 2001 October (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - "Gimme Danger," Opinion: To Each His Own, 2001 October (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - "Search and Destroy," Off the Map: Red Hot Chili Peppers, 2001 October 3 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Sky TV, "Search and Destroy", 2001 September (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - "Passenger," Mat Hoffman's Pro BMX II multi-media game, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Laurel Canyon movie posters, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Kramski, Kris, Larry Flint film America XXX, A Tribute to Sex and Rock & Roll, 2001 October 8 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Reichenbach, Fabienne, 2001 October 1 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Moët and Chandon, Sophie Megrous, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Solo Summer 2001 dates (Box 11, Folder 16-18)
  - MVO Summer dates, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 19-20)
  - Bug Music statement, July to September, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - MTV Latin Video Music Awards, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    Folder 22 contains two Flexplay DVDs, which are unplayable. One disc has been removed from its packaging to show the effects of oxidation. A Flexplay disc is stored in a vacuum-sealed package. There is a clear dye inside the disc, contained within the bonding resin of the disc, that reacts with oxygen. Approximately 48 hours after the seal is broken, the layer changes from clear to black, rendering the disc unplayable. If unopened, the shelf life of the sealed package is approximately a year. The DVD plastic also contains red dye, which prevents penetration of the disc by blue lasers that could go straight through the oxygen-reactive dye.
  - Christmas cards, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog," Prey For Rock & Roll, 2002 November 21 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog," "Doggystyle" sample, 2002 October 21 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - "Avenue B," This is Rock Ballad Gold, 2002 July 25 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - "No Fun," Dallas and Rusty, 2002 July 19 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Fastlane, FOX TV show, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - "Wild America," Hottest of the Hot, 2003 January 13 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog," Lock, Stock, and Two Smoking Barrels, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Brick By Brick / American Caesar 2-pack, 2002 December 4 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - "Cold Metal," Late Night eith David Letterman, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Peluce, Floyd, monthly reports, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Turner, Tina, DVD Simply the Best, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Mondo Picasso script, circa 1999 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - "Mask," Daredevil, 2003 January 7 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - "Raw Power," 16 Years of Alcohol, 2002 December 2 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Reflections of Evil DVD promo, circa 2003 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - "I'm Sick of You," Quitting Shelby, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - GHS Strings, 2003 January 13 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - SkyDog Records [RESTRCITED], 2003 January 10 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - "Tonight," Janis and John, 2003 January 16 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - "My Baby Wants to Rock N Roll," Rock, Australia, 2002 June 14 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - "I Need Somebody," Witchblade (and other song licensing), 2002 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Whiskey A Go-Go review [photocopy], 1988 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - "Beside You," Alternative Moments 2, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - "I'll Be See You," Doc Dog, Brazil, 2002 June 21 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - "Nightclubbing," Fiat, Holland, 2002 December 2 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - "Nightclubbing," DOA film, 2003 January 2 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Best of Bowie DVD release, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Grind costume department, 2002 October 10 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - "Candy," EMI Brazil, 2002 June 27 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - "Candy," Virgin Records, 2002 July 24 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - "Candy," Killerbabies, 2002 June 27 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - "China Girl," VH1 100 Sexiest Artists, 2002 September 24 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - "China Girl," American Idol, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - "China Girl," Last Call With Carson Daly, 2002 September 12 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - "Gimme Danger," Dogtown and Z-Boys, 2002 May 9 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - "Lust For Life," song licenses, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - "Passenger," song licenses, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - "Search and Destroy," song licenses, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Solo, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 61-62)
  - Stooges gigs, domestic, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Stooges gigs, international, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Thousand Mile, Inc., 2002 [RESTRICTED], 2003 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Solo offers, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Call sheets [RESTRICTED], 2004-2005 (Box 12, Folder 1-6, Box 11, Folder 67-68)
    Some of the materials in folders 6-8 are confidential and are, therefore, RESTRICTED. Access copies of these materials may have to be created prior to use. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
    Tour information can also be found in some of these folders.
  - Skull Ring, second file, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Codikow, Carroll, Guido, and Groffman, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Song licensing, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Radical Media, Academy Awards, 2002 February 19 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Meltdown, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Slash / David Helfant, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - HBO Sports, 2002 January 16 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Soundscan, 2002 January 3 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Grain, Jos, pay, Virgin UK, 2002 January (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Lahana, Alain, 2002, 2001 November 19 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - "I Need Somebody," Witchblade, Bug Music, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - "Lust For Life," Screen Cuts compilation, 2002 March 19 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - "Passenger," Screen Cuts compilation, 2002 March 19 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - "Bang, Bang," Laurel Canyon, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - "Raw Power," Leap of Faith, 2002 March (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - "Lust For Life," Beautiful Game, 2002 March 7 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - "Passenger," Punk boxset, 2002 February 28 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - "Nightclubbing," Hits From the Flicks, 2002 March 5 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - "Lust For Life," Hits From the Flicks, 2002 March 5 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - "Lust For Life," New Wave Classics, 2002 March 5 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - "Lust For Life," Royal Caribbean, 3rd renewal, 2002 April 26 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - "Lust For Life," NBC 75th Anniversary, 2002 March 21 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - "Passenger," Absolute Rock, 2002 January 8 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - "Techknowledgy," song licensing, 2002 August (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - "Lust For Life," Sims House Party, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Kraz, Richard, letter, 1991, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - "Waiting For the Man," Steve Cole, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Moët Champagne, Maria Conti, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Fitzgerald, Jim, correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Press clippings, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - 24 Hour Party People, clip use, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Santiago, Chile benefit, 2002 October 4 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Radical Media, AMC documentary, 2002 April 4 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Black Celebration, Jailbird films, 2002 April (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - New EMI, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Codikow, Carroll, Guido, and Groffman billing, 1999-2001 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Wolfman Productions / speaking engagements, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Rollins Publications, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Vacation movie script, 2002 March (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Bass, Gary, Chop Chop, film, 2001 October 15 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Moby dinner special Dinner and a Moby, 2002 April 10 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Doctoroff, Richard, information, Bulk, 2000-2002; 1991, 1997-2002 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    Regarding Thomas R. Copi and Andrew Sacks v. James Osterberg, aka Iggy Pop and 2.12.61 Publications, Inc.
  - Prey For Rock and Roll, Linda Cohen, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Q Magazine column request, 2002 April 12 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Concert on the Top of the World request, 2002 April 22 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Brigaudiot, Gui, French website, 2002 May 2 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - "Lust For Life," Best Alternative Album...Ever! CD, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - "Real Wild Child," World's Best Ever Beer Drinking Songs, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Belgium, DVD request Iggy Pop Live at the Avenue B, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Belgium concert, 2002 March 8 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Cold Metal," Radio Waves of the 80s, 2003 June 4 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - "Beside You," Alternative Moments, 2003 June 3 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - "Lust For Life," Magazine L'Espresso, Italy, 2003 June 12 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - "Idiot," EMI campaign, 2003 June 10 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Coffee and Cigarettes, movie, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - School of Rock, Wonderland, 2003 May 6 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - "Raw Power," Aloha Surf, 2003 May (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - "Lust For Life," Rugrats Go Wild, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - "No Fun," Lexus, Germany, 2003 April 10 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Simmons, Sylvie, correspondence, 2002 December 18 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - "Passenger," Escape Rock, 2003 May 27 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - "Search and Destroy," Wonderland, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog," Wonderland, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - "Aisha," Wrong Turn, 2003 April (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - "Aisha," Sonic Cinema, 2003 July (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - "Candy," Killer Barbys vs. Dracula, 2003 July 7 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - "Lust For Life," Munchies Music, 2003 July 8 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - "Candy," Mexico, Nu Classics, 2003 July 8 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - "Little Know It All," Nokia / Cingular, 2003 June 27 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - "Search and Destroy," Wire, 2003 June 9 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - "Rock and Roll Party," DVD for Japan, 2003 July 2 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - "Kiss My Blood," music distribution, 2003 March (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - "Search and Destroy," Hellacopters Live, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - "I'm Sick of You," School of ROck, 2003 June 30 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - "Lust For Life," Rugrats Go Wild Bug Music synch, 2003 July 18 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - "Candy," EMI Spain, 2003 June 30 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - "Search and Destroy," Haggard Soundtrack, 2003 July 1 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - "Lust For Life," Italy, Kiosks, 2003 June 13 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - "Lust For Life," Simpsons promo, 2003 October (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Lord of the Rings, image use, 2003 August 7 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - "Candy," Hang the DJ, 2003 August 14 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - "Lust For Life," Royal Caribbean, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - "Raw Power," Stander, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Millenia Nova, Bug Music, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - "Little Know It All," NASCAR Thunder 2004, 2003 July 16 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - "Lust For Life," Rugrats Go Wild, consent letters, 2003 May 19 (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - "Passenger," Virgin MegaMusic - Glam Rock, 2003 July 23 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - "Passenger," World's Best Ever Beer Songs 2004, 2003 July 29 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog," Ongoing History of New Music, 2003 July 21 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - "Nightclubbing," Trolleywood, 2003 July 29 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - "Lust For Life," EMi Party Box Set, 2003 July 11 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - "1970," Tony Hawk's Underground, 2003 July 2 (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - "Search and Destroy," Wonderland, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - "Lust For Life," Overdrive Me Crazy, 2003 July 10 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - "Candy," Indie Anthems #3, 2003 July 14 (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - "Passenger," Best Air Guitar Album in the World... Ever! Vol. 2 CDs, 2003 July 11 (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - Bug Music Statements, January to March, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - "Lust For Life," EMI "Gold Box" and Rock Heroes, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - T.V. Eye, budget series, 2003 December 9 (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - "Passenger," Rockline, Volume 2, 2003 November 17 (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - "Little Know It All," "46th Grammy's", 2003 December 12 (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - "Passenger," Mercedes Benz, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - "Lust For Life," Mitsubishi Mix CD, 2003 December (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - "Gimme Danger," "Search and Destory," Life Aquatic, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - "Lust For Life," Rugrats Go Wild, heir letters, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - "Passenger," 70 A L'Heure, 2003 May 13 (Box 12, Folder 110)
  - "Search and Destroy," skate video, 2003 May 14 (Box 12, Folder 111)
  - "Passenger," Tommy Hilfger CD, 2003 May 22 (Box 12, Folder 112)
  - "Lust For Life," 20th Century Masters, 2003 May 21 (Box 12, Folder 113)
  - Bourne Supremacy, poster use, 2003 November 12 (Box 12, Folder 114)
  - "Passenger," Time-Life Classics, 2003 November 12 (Box 12, Folder 115)
  - "Lust For Life," Las 101 Mejores Canciones Del Rock, 2003 November 5 (Box 12, Folder 116)
  - "Lust For Life," Don Cherry's Hockey Hits, Vol. II, 2003 October 6 (Box 12, Folder 117)
  - "Lust For Life," La Republica (Italy), 2003 October 15 (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - "Search and Destroy," Haggard, skateboards, 2003 May (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - Life Aquatic, licensing, 2003 October (Box 12, Folder 120)
  - "Lust For LIfe," Greenpeace, 2003 October 15 (Box 12, Folder 121)
  - "Candy," 100% Rolling Stone II, 2003 October 22 (Box 12, Folder 122)
  - "Louie Louie," French perfume, 2003 October 17 (Box 12, Folder 123)
  - "Nightclubbing," ringtone use, 2003 October 8 (Box 12, Folder 124)
  - "Motor Inn," Clubbers Guide to 2004, 2003 December 4 (Box 12, Folder 125)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog," That '70s Show, 2003 October (Box 12, Folder 126)
  - "Lust For Life," Roxy Club and Rock, 2003 November 10 (Box 12, Folder 127)
  - Hoskyns, Barry, book proposal, 2003 February 18 (Box 12, Folder 128)
    This file includes an E-mailed copy of the October 1986 New Musical Express article by Hoskyns, "Iggy Pop: Animal God of the Street."
  - "Moonlight Lady," "My Baby Wants to Rock and Roll," Virgin 30th Anniversary, 2003 April 8 (Box 12, Folder 129)
  - "Passenger," Discotheque Ideale, 2003 April 10 (Box 12, Folder 130)
  - "Candy," Play My Music, Volume 1, 2003 April 2 (Box 12, Folder 131)
  - "Lust For Life,' "Modern Edge", 2003 April 1 (Box 12, Folder 132)
  - "Search and Destroy," Wire, 2003 April (Box 12, Folder 133)
  - I Need More, book information, 1991-1995, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Wood, Keith [RESTRICTED], 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 2-4)
    Some of the materials in folder 2 are confidential and are, therefore, RESTRICTED. Access copies of these materials may have to be created prior to use. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
  - Gelman, Anita, contracts, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Receipts [RESTRICTED], 2003 (Box 14, Folder 1-4, Box 13, Folder 6-7)
  - Song licensing, 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 5-7)
  - Album information Skull Ring, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 8-10)
  - "I'm Sick of You" t-shirt, 2003 April 17 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Skeleton Key, t-shirt usage, 2004 March 8 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - DeCeglie, Mauro, Virgin products, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 13-15)
  - Virgin press, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - de Vries, Simone, Importance of Being Iggy, 2003 August 12 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Virgin International, promotion requests, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Recording proposal, 2002 July 10 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Zombie Birdhouse, New Millenium proposal, 1995, 1999, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Royalties Reunited, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Anthill Trading, Ltd., 2003 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Licensing contracts, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Solo Japan, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - "Bad Boyz," special delivery, 2004 August 11 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Coachella gig [RESTRICTED], 2001, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - "Lust For Life," Simpsons, 2004 September 9 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - "I'm Bored," VH1 Totally Obsessed, 2004 August (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - "Passenger," Drew Barrymore, 2004 August 20 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - "Success," ski video, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - "Passenger," I Love TV Ads, 2004 August 25 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - "Lust For Life," Veronica Mars, 2004 August 17 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - "Boogie Boy," Crossing Jordan, 2004 August (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - "Lust For Life," Royal Caribbean [RESTRICTED], 2004 September 1 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - "Motor Inn," Virgin dance compilation, "Lust For Life," Huff, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog," Friday Night Lights, 2004 July 27 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - "Lust For Life," Pure Punk Impact, Vol. 2, 2004 August 10 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - "Passenger," Pure Punk Impact, Vol. 1, 2004 August 10 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Bowie, David, Reality Tour, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - "Little Know It All," Summerland TV show, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - "Passenger," 50 Anni Di Rock, Vol. 5, 2004 June 24 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You," Coffee Company, 2004 June 16 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - "Passenger," Rock TV Classics, 2004 June 24 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - "Little Know It All," Iggy Pop, Deryck Whibley contract, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - "Motor Inn," Dance Star Awards, 2004 May 25 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - "Whatever," Razzmatazz, 2004 May 20 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - "Lust For Life," Radio 2 Top 70, Deel 2, 2004 May 28 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - "Lust For Life," Borders Rack Essentials, Volume 3, 2004 June 4 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - "Passenger," Lost in Translation, 2004 April (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - "Lust For Life," Royal Caribbean website, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Reed, Lou, Max's Kansas City Project, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Bug Music statements, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Bug Music licensing, 2000, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Life Aquatic licensing, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Grumble Corporation, foreign insurance, 2002, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - South Bank Show, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Shure microphones, 2004 August 13 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Gelman, Anita, settlement, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Cadavera, Mick McCarthy film, circa 2004 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Europe promo, 2004 March (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Song licensing, circa 2004 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Anthill Trading, Ltd., 2004 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - DeCeglie, Mauro, Virgin, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Soundscan reports, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Smith, Steve, Search and Destroy screenplay, 2003 December 1 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Sales, Hunt, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Floyd Peluce CPA statements, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Skull Ring, Soundscan, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Fat Possum Records contract, 2003 August 11 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - "TV Eye," Nissan Xterra, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Brady, David, advertising, 2003 December (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Virgin radio promotion, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - "Search and Destroy," Volkswagen, 2004 May (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - "Candy," Con Nombre De Mujer, 2004 May 14 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - "Little Know It All," Summerland, 2004 May 18 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - "Passenger," Weatherman, 2004 July (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - "1969," Dick Rude, Joe Strummer Let's Rock Again, 2004 May 25 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Escovedo, Alejandro, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Coffee and Cigarettes, United Artists, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Hellhounds Pooch Wear, 2003 December 9 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Bowie, David, book - Myriam Santos-Kayda, 2004 January 14 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Funhouse art show, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Greece Olympics, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - "Lust For Life," Comedy Central Odd Todd, 2004 July 21 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - "I Feel Alright," Thumbsucker, 2004 July (Box 15, Folder 19)